{
    "quizzes": [
        {
            "question": "The simplest among the various \ntexturing methods is not image texturing.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "A texture is typically represented \nas a 2D array of texels texture elements.",
            "answer": "O"
        },
        {
            "question": "A texels location can not be \ndescribed by the coordinates of its center.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "Image texturing is often described as \npasting an image on an objects surface.",
            "answer": "O"
        },
        {
            "question": "The most popular lighting method is \nnot based on the Phong model.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Phong model is composed of four terms: \n diffuse, specular, ambient and emissive.",
            "answer": "O"
        },
        {
            "question": "The diffuse term is \nnot based on Lamberts law.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lambertian surfaces are not scattered\n with equal intensity in all directions.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "The amount of perceived reflection is\n not independent of the view direction",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fragment shader has not processed\n the fragments in the viewport.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "Color buffer is not a memory space storing\n the pixels to be displayed on the screen.",
            "answer": "X"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the fragment has a smaller zvalue,\n its color and zvalue are used to\n update the color buffer and zbuffer",
            "answer": "O"
        }
    ]
}